Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series
are fictional and created
for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
I’m Key.
This is my first day working here.
I met someone.
So this one night, it must be really good.
You don’t seem to have a money problem.
Why do you want to be my sugar baby?
I just want to be your girl.
I chose to get the moon tattoo
because of you.
You are my first love.
Have we met before?
I won’t tell you if we have met.
You have to remember it yourself.
Mom.
-Mom.
-Miss.
-Key.
Mom
What happened to my wife?
There’s not much I can tell you right now.
We need to wait for the autopsy results
to know her cause of death.
I need your daughter to come
to the station to give her statement.
Why?
Because she is the first person
who discovered the body.
This is my fault, Dad.
She is dead because I came back home.
Key, don’t say anything.
It’s my fault that she is dead.
Key.
Honey, don’t say that.
It’s my fault that she is dead.
It’s not your fault.
It’s my fault.
Key, don’t do this.
Key.
It’s my fault that she is dead.
It’s not your fault.
I shouldn’t have come back.
Key.
Tonight is a new moon night.
Is that so?
So what?
They say a new moon, or a moonless night,
it marks a new beginning.
It’s a chance to wash away the negative
and transform into
a new version of ourselves.
It’s a good time
for those who want to forget
the bad things in their past
or for those who have done bad things.
Tonight is a good chance.
Is something going on with you?
Yes.
Something big is going on.
What is it?
I want to be your sugar baby.
Why do you keep saying the same thing?
This is the last time I’ll ask you.
If you don’t want me to talk about it,
then you need to give me your answer.
What are you going to do about us?
Why do you want to be my sugar baby?
It will be fun.
I like being your little sugar baby.
You are strange.
If I’m not strange,
you won’t remember me.
Do you have anything else
for me to remember,
besides your strange offer?
Something else to remember?
What else could it be?
Pretty sis.
If you want to be my sugar baby,
you need to follow my rules.
Rules?
I can do anything to you.
But you need to do everything I tell you.
You are mine only.
But it doesn’t mean
that I will have only you.
Then what am I to you?
My sugar baby.
I own you.
I’m your boss.
Are you okay with it?
If not,
then we will go our separate ways.
Okay.
I’ll be your sugar baby.
Are you sure you are okay with it?
A woman like you is so my type.
I like you.
I’ll remind you again.
Between us, I’m your employer.
You are my employee.
And…
You are my personal entertainer.
No one can know about our deal.
Roger that.
Are you going to spend tonight with me?
So I can start providing my service.
Key.
What’s wrong?
Why are you sleeping here?
Simba kept waking me.
So I came out to give him wet cat food.
But he refused to eat it.
So I boiled chicken for him.
He also refused to eat it.
Let me take a look.
Key.
Get up. Go get dressed.
Where are we going?
We’ll take Simba to see a vet.
We don’t need to. This is typical of him.
He’s just a free spirit.
If you refuse to eat,
is it because you’re sick,
or you’re just a free spirit?
Sick.
Don’t worry. I’ll take you to a vet.
Let’s take him to a vet.
It’s okay, Simba.
I’ll take you to a vet.
If I hadn’t insisted on
taking Simba to a vet,
we wouldn’t have known he was sick.
You need to take better care of him.
What would you do
if his sickness was serious?
Alright.
I was wrong.
I’ll take Simba to live with me
until he gets better.
Huh?
Are you serious?
Yes.
If you leave him alone to go to work
and there’s an emergency,
what will you do?
I won’t let anything happen to him.
Simba’s mom, please go get his medication.
Yes.
We are both his moms.
I’m his mommy.
She is…
his mama.
Mama and Mommy,
please go get his medication.
Yes.
Let’s go.
Can you get my bag for me?
Wait for me, Mama.
Hi, Jay.
Do you want a coffee?
No.
Did Chan know
that I’m your business partner?
Are you sure you want to do this?
You need to help me get Chan back.
Otherwise, I won’t help you
with the debt you owe me.
I think…
If you don’t want it to become public,
you’d better make your move to help me.
Take off your shoes here.
Okay.
Put on the slippers.
We are home, Simba.
Do you like it?
Do you like a big room like this?
You can put Simba’s stuff in that room.
Yes.
I’ll put you down.
Do you like my room?
It’s big, right?
You like it?
Your meow means you like it, doesn’t it?
You enjoy this, don’t you?
Why do you never look at me
the way you look at Simba?
Are you a cat?
But I’m the cat’s mommy.
Meow.
Simba, do you want to come out?
Let’s go enjoy the view.
Do you like it?
Chan.
Can I take a nap?
I don’t want to fall asleep
on stage tonight.
Sure.
You are so kind.
Hold on.
Yes?
Where are you going?
I’m going to take a nap.
You can take a nap
on the sofa.
That’s my bed.
Fine.
I’ll lie down properly.
Thank you.
How are you doing?
I feel much better.
You want to talk to me
about my birthday party, right?
Yes.
I want you to invite Key to your party.
I don’t think I can.
I think we should give it another try.
I mean, I can’t do that
because I won’t hold
a birthday party this year.
I…
I’m really busy with the farm business.
I have many things to handle.
I think I’ll need to stay there
for several days.
But this is your birthday.
Just seeing you healthy again
is the best gift for me.
But I want all of us
to be together this year.
Please.
It’s up to Key.
I…
I don’t want to force her.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Did you pretend to be sleeping?
No.
I was sleeping.
But you smell so good.
When you come close to me,
your scent wakes me up.
You little perv.
You are doing it first.
What do you mean?
I haven’t done anything.
I’m just checking if you are breathing.
So you’re worried about me.
So sweet of you.
But are you sure
you’re just checking my breathing?
Don’t you want to check everything
like you did last night?
You should go home.
But it’s not time for my work.
I still have several hours left.
Where am I going to hang out?
That’s your business, not mine.
But…
Go.
Okay, I’ll leave.
I’ll go to practice with my band.
It doesn’t matter
if you act cold towards me
or always have to get your own way,
as long as I can be by your side
and see your smile,
that’s enough for me.
Go.
Fine, I’m leaving.
Sis.
Who are you?
What’s your name?
Whose cat is it?
Can I hold you?
Come on.
You are so chubby.
Let me take a look at you.
What’s your name?
Why are you here?
When did you have a cat?
He’s not my cat.
I take care of him for his owner.
Who is the owner?
You wouldn’t know her even if I told you.
This is not good.
There’s no way you would
take care of a cat for someone,
especially someone I don’t know.
What happened to you?
You are overstating.
No, I’m not.
I’m your twin sister.
I know you well.
She just asked me to take care of him.
He’s sick.
You are sick?
That’s why you look lethargic.
I didn’t know that you liked animals.
Me too.
I never thought that I would like cats.
Tell me who his owner is
and what she does for a living.
You wouldn’t know her even if I told you.
Does this mean you got over Jay?
Why did you come to see me today?
If you don’t have any business with me,
you should leave, Sun.
Today is my day off.
I want to spend time alone.
Based on your answer,
I guess you are not over her.
Fine, I’ll leave.
I know that my words upset you.
But seriously,
when are you going to get over her?
We meet again.
Don’t tell me that you’re also
a regular customer at this bar?
You’re almost right.
I’m a regular singer here.
I started to work here recently.
Really?
Yes.
I told you we would
run into each other often.
Do you think it’s destiny?
Maybe.
But our destiny is to be friends.
I guess your relationship
with that person,
it’s no longer just a one-night stand.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
If you’re dating that person for a year,
will you still feel excited
when kissing her?
I think so.
Why?
Remember my words.
Kissing a person you like,
it’s like smoking.
You only feel excited
when it’s the first kiss.
What do you mean?
After a while,
it will become a habit,
and you'll get addicted to it.
Even when you want to quit,
you can’t.
What if I always feel
excited when doing it?
It means you are lucky.
You’ve found the one.
So don’t make a mistake.
Don’t let her go.
Key, there you are.
It’s almost time for our band to perform.
Okay, I’ll be right there.
You can go watch my band.
See you.
You like it?
Do you like this toy?
Catch it.
One, two, three, jump.
Let me take pictures of you.
Simba, look at the camera.
One, two, three.
Simba.
Let’s take a selfie.
Wow, you look at the camera.
Wait here.
Look, who is here to see you?
It seems that
Simba is getting much better now.
I’ll take him home.
I don’t want to bother you any longer.
You should leave.
I’ll keep him with me tonight
to monitor his condition.
How can you do that?
He’s my cat.
I think I can take care of him
better than you.
How about this?
I’ll sleep over here tonight.
I’ll help you take care of him.
I’ll go home tomorrow.
Are you using this
as an excuse to stay the night?
You did sleep over at my place.
Why can’t I sleep over here?
Fine.
But you will sleep on the sofa.
Can I sleep with you in bed?
You’re just a sugar baby.
You can sleep in my bed
only on special occasions.
Then I’ll make tonight a special occasion.
Someone told me this.
Kissing is like smoking.
We get excited only the first time.
Come on, Simba.
Let’s go to bed.
Where did he go?
Simba.
Why do you say things so similarly?
Let’s go to bed.
Good night.
It’s been a while, Sun.
It’s good to see you.
You can drop your act, Jay.
I know you hate me.
You’re still the same.
No matter how much you two look alike,
I can’t bring myself to like you.
Why did you come back?
You are so brazen to come back here.
Sun, you are normally a sweet person.
Why are you so rude to me today?
I’m selective about how I treat people.
I’m nice to everyone
except those who f*ck my sister up.
I just came back to get what is mine back.
Do you think
my sister will let you fool her again?
Love is not about being smart or stupid.
It’s about finding a good match.
If we are a good match,
no one can come between us.
♪ Just look into my eyes
a little while longer ♪
♪ Every action will make
the memory stronger ♪
♪ Let your feelings slowly grow ♪
♪ And you will remember only me ♪
Chan.
Did I wake you up?
What is the title of the song?
It’s a song that I’m writing.
I’ve never performed it for anyone.
You are the first person
to hear this song.
It’s beautiful.
I like it.
Can you sing it again?
Why don’t you sing along with me?
♪ Just look into my eyes
a little while longer ♪
♪ Let your heart get closer to mine ♪
♪ Try to explore what love truly means ♪
♪ One night is not enough for us ♪
♪ I want to love you every day ♪
♪ Close to me, you only one ♪
♪ I’ll make you love and remember me ♪
♪ I’ll keep showing you
until you love me ♪
♪ Every touch will remind you of me ♪
♪ Every embrace and every action
will make the memory stronger ♪
♪ Let your feelings slowly grow ♪
♪ And you will remember only me ♪
It’s beautiful.
Why don’t you finish the song?
Sure.
But…
Don’t you have something else
you want me to do right now?
You’re a little perv.
Do you like it?
Yes.
From now on,
I have a new rule.
The two of us,
we will not kiss.
We can’t kiss? What do you want me to do?
We won’t kiss.
This is a strict rule.
Do you get it?
It will be hard for me.
Why do we need to have this rule?
You don’t need to know the reason.
Just do what I told you to do.
Since you won’t let me
kiss you on the lips,
can you kiss my tattoo instead?
♪ You're surely right ♪
♪ You don’t love me
for just one day, right? ♪
♪ Will you stay with me
through days and nights? ♪
♪ Each morning,
will I see your face next to mine? ♪
♪ You’re not just making my heart waver ♪
♪ Then leave me forever, no ♪
Simba, get off me. You’re heavy.
Simba.
We can’t kiss.
So you do this instead.
I want your restaurant
to launch a sale promotion for my hotel.
You will offer 15% off all meal courses
for the hotel guests for one year.
In return, I’ll agree to let you
open your restaurant in my hotel.
And I won’t charge you rent
for the first month.
About that.
I need to ask my partner first.
Who is your partner?
Phu.
Tell me.
Sun.
Who is helping you?
What did you know?
Chan, I…
Hi.
Do you miss me?
Your restaurant.
It’s Jay’s plan, isn’t it?
I’m sorry.
Jay ordered me to do it.
I’m in a tough spot myself.
I know Chan won’t be okay with it.
Is it because you owe Jay money?
Phu.
You end up like this because
you’re living above your means.
I know that you borrowed money
from many people.
Even the director I work with,
you also borrowed money from him.
But I never flake on them.
I’m gradually paying them back.
I’m never late on my payment.
But the money that you pay them back,
it’s Jay’s money.
We’ve known each other
for a long time, Phu.
You are Chan’s friend.
If you continue to do this,
I will cut you off one day.
I miss you.
Don’t be mad at Phu.
I forced him to do this.
I told you.
I really want to do business with you.
Don’t let our relationship
be a problem for the business.
I’m asking you.
It won’t affect the restaurant.
It’s a business.
You just do your work.
It has nothing to do with me.
You are the same.
This is my Chan.
Will you have dinner with me tonight?
I knew it.
If you are done with your business,
you should leave.
Before I leave,
can I have a goodbye kiss?
Do you remember I told you this?
Kissing is like smoking.
I quit smoking for a while.
But when I see it again.
I’m more excited
than the first time I smoked.
Do you feel the same as I do?
Fine.
I’m leaving.
See you.
It’s beautiful.
Really?
Do you want to play with me?
Why isn’t she home yet?
Simba, you miss Mama too, right?
Chan smells so good.
Don’t touch my piano.
I’m sorry.
You have no right to touch my stuff
without my permission,
especially this piano.
Do you get it?
Yes.
I get it.
Sorry.
I just don’t like
when people touch my piano.
Can I ask?
What’s the matter with this piano?
This piano,
it belongs to someone who hurt me.
Someone I don’t want to talk about.
I promise.
I will never touch this piano again.
I will also keep Simba away from it.
If it’s Simba,
I don’t mind.
What?
You are playing favorites.
Why?
Do you have a problem with that?
No.
As your sugar baby,
I will never hurt you.
I will never make you feel stressed
or upset.
In the time we spend together,
you will feel only happiness.
From now on, making you smile
It will be my main duty.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
When you smile like this,
I’m in trouble.
Why?
I’m just your sugar baby.
I can’t kiss you.
When I see you smile,
I want to kiss you.
Since you’re my sugar baby,
you can kiss me on the cheek.
I’ll let you do it.
Then I’ll do it.
The kiss on the forehead is a bonus.
Chan.
This girl.
Who is she?
What are you doing here?
I just want to try your hotel service.
I think she wants to get back with you.
What are you thinking,
being her sugar baby?
Bye.
Why are you doing this, Key?
We broke up, Jay. Don’t do this.
But now I’m back.
What if Chan refuses to get back with you?
I want you to move on.
I want you to know that this is my job.
I’ll help you forget her.
You will remember only me.